Yes.
Good morning.
And.
OK, so let's uh.
You'll be happy to know that I only have
three slides to show you today,
and this is one of them. So um.
Today we're going to start off with AI
practitioner resources.
This is an application I created that I
has, I think,
a lot of bearing on what we're doing in
the course,
and so I think that you'll find it
interesting. Christopher, no questions.
We don't see your screen.
I thought I shared,
but I obviously didn't make a mistake.
Let's go ahead. Can you see it now?
Yes, thanks.
Thank you for pointing that out.
So we're going to look at AI practitioner
resources. Again,
I think this this has a lot of bearing on
what we've been talking about in this
course.
Yeah.
So I think that you'll see some
interesting things there.
Then I want to do a prompt for you after
the after the day yesterday I went
through and.
Ransom additional prompts.
So I want to go through those prompts
with you so that you understand where we
stand with the project right now and then
we'll get into implementing slices and
that'll be the majority of the day.
We're going to spend coding or having AIS
assistance in coding implementations and
going through the.
Process of building these licenses and
see how far we can get into actually
completing this application. All right.
Any questions before we get started?
I got a question. You know,
we are supposed to set up a bunch of
tools and a couple of them were like the
Pandac and the Mark.
Yeah.
Are you gonna just go over those today?
I hadn't planned on it.
These are tools that I thought you might
have an interest in using since that what
I'm using it for is I can use a I to
generate a slide on a particular topic or
a deck of slides and then I can convert
them into a PowerPoint and then and then
incorporate them.
And modify them into a slide presentation.
So if you ever if you're doing any kind
of that work,
these tools might be useful to you,
but they're not directly related to the
course.
They're just they're just tools like that
are optional that you can take advantage
of.
I see. OK,
and I'm I'm sure they're probably pretty
self-explanatory.
Yeah, they're not hard to use,
but and they provide a lot of value,
so I thought I'd mentioned them.
Other questions?
All right,
so let's take a look at that AI resources
page.
Let me tell you a little bit about it.
So this is this is what it looks like.
This is the URL where you can find it and
I I I built this using a I first and
prompt first techniques.
The whole this whole page was built by a
I.
With my assisting me,
essentially I drove the process,
but it wrote all the content and and
builds all the content.
So started off with basically a simple
request from from somebody had taken the
course,
wanted to know if I had a list of
resources that they could.
Review maybe, you know,
blog posts or books or the like.
And so I of course in a prompt first
manner I I asked AI to produce a a a list
of resources and and as going through
that process I it came to me that well
that list of resources.
I send out would be good today,
but it would likely not be relevant or as
relevant in a month or six months away.
So I had a thought of how can I automate
the execution of that prompt?
And so that it it's it would refresh this
page with new content on a regular basis.
And so that's what this is trying to do.
It has during the in the course of
actually building this out,
you know new features.
Occurred to me. And so I just, you know,
as I went along, I actually, you know,
continue to extend this.
And there's a couple of interesting
features about this that I think you
might be interested in. One is that,
you know, every.
Every Sunday evening a a GitHub action is
triggered.
The GitHub action then executes a prompt
that returns data for the page in a.
A Jason BLOB and then that Jason BLOB
gets stored into a GitHub gist.
So the whole page is built on basically
two infrastructure pieces.
One is GitHub's ability to serve up.
A static pages from a repository,
which is what this is,
and then the GitHub's ability to store
data in what GitHub calls a gist,
which is just a a repository.
That has a a very easy interface that you
can use to put data into and retrieve
data out of.
So the data that you're seeing here is
stored in a a gist in GitHub and it's
rendered to a static page and so
effectively this is self-contained within
the GitHub universe and as long as.
GitHub is up and running.
This page should be up and running as
well,
so it it pulls in a few resources and
then it compares that with the the
previous run of this and.
Starts to calculate things like how long
it's been on the list.
It shows you here what what kind of a a
piece of information is because it tries
to retrieve articles, books,
podcasts and blogs.
And then over here is a a series of of
ratings that it that.
The A I has determined that how it
performs in terms of seven principal risk
factors.
So it's looking for does this particular
resource address security vulnerabilities?
Does it address logic and quality issues?
Does it address data data leakage?
Does it address licensing concerns,
maintainability problems,
bias and inconsistent standards or or and
or over reliance?
Which could lead to skill atrophy and you
can see that his this has got a score of
95 on security vulnerabilities and it you
would expect it to score high because of
the the secure code review.
Guide.
So that would we would expect that to
score high there and it scored fairly
high in quality and logic,
a bit lower in maintainability and
documentation,
even lower in bias and and standards
detection.
And a little bit better in in dealing
with over reliance and skills so that.
So again the A I is examining each of the
resources that it finds and gives it a
score on on these seven principles.
If you don't see a principle listed,
it was determined that it.
It doesn't really address that particular
risk strongly,
so therefore it doesn't include it in the
list and and then it ranks ranks them
here in terms of what the highest score
for any one of these individual thing
these ratings so that.
So we see if it scores high in one and
low in the other ones,
it's still considered a a strong resource
to put to include in the on the page.
So it also then captures or produces a a
brief synopsis of what the actual content
contains and so so you can see.
Here that we have here a a book called
Building Secure and Relatable Systems
that you can get from from Google.
Here is a article that's been posted
about software composition analysis.
And so you can see there's a number of
different resources that are that are
provided that that are exposed by this.
And so this is a just a good page in and
of itself just to just to find resources
that might address a particular.
A particular area within a I assisted
software development that might be useful
for you. So in addition to that,
it also produces an analysis of all from
the of all the all of the resources that
were found and gives you a kind of an
overview of what this particular week's.
Content consists of and then it has some
some basically boilerplate leaks of links
at the bottom that tells you information
about it,
things that you can do related to this,
what the methodology that it's using to
make this determination. So it's.
Using a risk-based scoring system on a on
a scale of 1 to 100 and then it looks at
you know,
some financial security vulnerabilities
is looking for frameworks for identifying
and mitigating security flaws in an AI
generated code. So this tells us what the.
The criteria are for evaluating each
resource and one thing I think is
interesting about this is that it's again,
it's built with AI first and and prompt
first principles.
So you know I started with a with a
prompt with the original idea on
gathering these resources.
And then I'm continually prompting the AI
to to adjust the implementation or to
improve the process,
but it also has an AI from an AI first
perspective, it's, you know, running.
It's basically what it's doing is running
in it through GitHub actions,
executing prompts in the in on the back
end and and processing that information.
It does that in a number of different
areas and it it the way in which I'm in
designing this for contributions that
instead of submitting a pull request you
would submit a prompt.
That and then the AI would evaluate that
prompt in terms of the quality of the
implementation prompt,
and if it finds that it's lacking in in
its criteria for an acceptable piece of
code to implement,
it then adds a comment to the.
To the issue that's created for that
particular prompt and and then which
notifies the submitter that that there is
something that needs to be addressed
about their prompt and for them to to
make a change and resubmit it.
And and that can repeat until the A I
decides that it's got enough information
in this prompt to actually consider
implementing it.
And then once the A I has reviewed it and
determined that that that's the case,
then that goes to a human review to
actually review the the prompt.
And if it's approved by a human reviewer,
then it would go into the implementation
queue and then A I would pick it up and
execute the the prompt in order to do the
an implementation and then on the back
end after the implementation it goes
through a process of.
Um.
Of evaluating the implementation and
using a technique like I was talking or
talked about earlier where you're
actually asking a couple of a is their
opinion of of a particular implementation.
And if they agree that it's a a good
implementation,
then it would go for a human review for
the final approval of that particular
implementation and then that.
If that's approved, it would go.
It would be submitted into the code base
and deployed with the next deployment.
So that's that.
Now the other thing that you can do with
this is that you can then you can go to
the the, the, the,
you can go to GitHub and you can actually
look at the entire implementation.
So this may actually have some techniques
in it and some code in it that you
actually might want to take it.
Take advantage of and take a look at.
You can see the prompts that I'm running.
You can see the how it's being,
how it's set up and how and there's a
fairly comprehensive state model that
describes.
How how prompts go from being submitted
all the way through to being implemented
and which I've I'm working my way through
that state chart to get all of the
features that I want to see implemented
in the process implemented.
So I just wanted to point this to you
because I think it's a a good example of
what a I first and prompt first
development looks like and and I think
you might get some value from actually
taking a look at it.
So any questions on this about how it was
produced or?
So can we look at the GitHub project or?
Oh yeah, I mean,
you can just click on the link and it'll
Oh.
take you right here into into the into
the repo and here you can see.
Um.
You know what's in the GitHub folder,
et cetera.
Which will contain the prompts that I'm
running.
What the workflows are, some automation,
some documentation.
So and again this this is something that
if you're interested in you can you just
send it'll you can hit the link that says
I want to be a a contributor which will
cater toward an issue in GitHub and I can
then.
You know,
approve you and you can start to actually
submit code reviews and make and suggest
modifications.
And the only caveat is that I'm
preferring to to take modifications based
on implementation prompts so that they
build a prompt, submit the prompt.
And then we can then I then I can
consider it.
And a good way to doing that would be to
potentially, you know,
clone it or fork it and then you can test
out your prompts locally and then once
you're happy with them,
you can then submit them.
For inclusion in the actual page.
So yeah,
so if you're looking to kind of a,
you know,
have a practice place for it or or or
examine existing product that's out there
on the on the web that's actually being
deployed and executed,
you can take a look at this project and
it.
It might give you some ideas. Um.
Other questions on this?
Alrighty then.
I I know you verbally mentioned the the
the flow of how things are going to be
going through on this project.
Is there a diagram of that that maybe
could be added?
I I I I showed one yes to to talk about
for this this particular project or just?
To this.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
This one that you just talked through and
said this is how it's going to work and
you know the the processes along the way
of of where the PRS occur and and how
things get approved for updates.
To the code base is is there.
Any kind of uh just like a flow diagram
showing what the steps are?
Um.
Yeah, alright,
let me put that in here somewhere.
Where is the?
It's not a test.
But.
Let me see if I can open this up in a
browser from here.
So I think this might do it.
Nope.
I think this is the, yeah,
the state charts.
Let me, uh,
let me bring up the project locally and
then see if I can bring up that page.
All right, so let's see.
I don't have that project open,
so let me another instance of Visual
Studio code.
And let me open a folder.
And.
All right,
just give me a second to navigate to
where it's at.
Where it's at.
I'm not sure we're seeing the right
screen.
Yeah,
I'm just going through and navigate
Oh, talking.
folders right now.
This looks like the right one.
And uh, was it the?
If you like cycle.
You know this looks like it,
so let me just open this in a new window.
So it says the diagram worked
successfully, but I don't see it.
Let me try the other one, the other one.
All right, so back here was two of these.
It's been a month since I've been in this
code base, so.
Mhm.
It wants me to close that browser window.
So I'll do that.
Can you try it again?
Alright, so I.
All right, so here's the state machine.
See if I zoom in on this a little bit.
Alright.
And I can scroll and pan,
but it looks like it's.
A little challenge with the display,
so something that's still needs a little
bit of work.
But anyway,
you can see this diagram that has um.
Uh.
It basically is trying to document a a
state model that.
Uh.
Not I wish I could see the whole thing.
Anyway,
what it does is and you can see here that
it has some concepts.
What issues are being worked on?
It goes through the process of, you know,
things that are actually being worked on
right now.
Here's the copilot code review portions
of it.
So this will kind of describe exactly
what I've been thinking of in terms of
how to actually go through and.
Run things to to where is that where the
issue is finally closed in GitHub.
I can't show you the whole thing but.
OK,
so this is explaining how like every
Sunday something kicks off and then this
is the process that it goes through for
it to eventually become an updated.
OK.
Published web page, right?
Not quite this.
What this is asking me having to do with
Oh.
if if if an issue is submitted with the
prompts,
how does that issue get reviewed
evaluated?
Queued for implementation, implemented,
reviewed and then for approved for
actually deployment.
So this is the process that you would use
to say if I wanted to modify the prompt
that is going out to retrieve the
resources, let's say that you wanted to,
you know, change the criteria.
Material for selecting resources for
inclusion in the page,
you would submit a prompt to do that and
then you could then that missus would say
how that prompt would be evaluated to the
point where it could be pushed into the
the repo. Does that make sense?
Right. So if you right,
I mean because if you wanted to see the
OK.
Alright.
code that's implemented that updates the
page,
you could go into the repo and you can
see what the GitHub action is that fires
off that page refresh and then.
And then how how that how that GitHub
action then calls to the A I to actually
execute the the prompt so that it gets
back a response and then how that
response is then turned into this the the
the page that you see when it's gets
rendered.
So that's one thing that you can you can
you can look at.
The other thing that would be that's
interesting about it is because of the
architecture you can pretty much plug and
play the the main query to do whatever
you to retrieve with resources on
whatever topic that you want.
So if you're a big.
Fan of knitting.
You could do the same thing with build a
set very similar page to that just by
changing the the core prompt that's
actually retrieving the information.
All right. Any questions here?
OK.
Anyway, take a look at it.
If you have questions,
you know you can post something on on the
GitHub page and I'll be happy to to go
over it with you. But yeah,
I think it's relevant for the course
because it does that A I it was, you know,
built A I first and prompt first.
You know,
from the very start and it came together
very, very quickly. No matter of,
you know,
part-time work for a couple of weeks,
I had something up and running and it was
pretty, I think, pretty sophisticated.
So that so I'm pretty happy with this.
Implementation so far. Yeah, Dan.
Yeah, so I'm looking on the GitHub,
the actions tab.
So is this so when so when someone
submits something it fires off a a new
Mhm.
action?
Yes, that's right.
Um.
Right.
So that if I look at the contributor
request,
that's what that there's one on November
17th,
that's that's what got fired from like
the back end of the code, is that right?
Well, if it's a contributor request,
it's something that's going in just
basically directly into the issues from
GitHub.
I'm not really interacting with that.
That's for me to review,
but if you submit something that is a
prompt, then.
That's where I would it would take a look
at it and and actually evaluate the
prompt in terms of this for its ability
to actually be implemented and then
respond with with essentially comments on
the.
On the issue that you're creating.
Indicating what needed to be improved in
order to make it something that could be
executable.
I see.
Is there is there an example of one of
Right.
these?
Like is it on the actions tab that would
Well,
you can take a look at the the issue
be an example of this?
backlog and you can see the things that
are kind of queued up there.
Some of them have gone through this
process and some of them haven't.
Which means I've created them directly
and I'm going to be using to implement
them.
Right,
so my goal is to is to whittle down on
that backlog and and get the rest of this
state chart implemented.
OK,
so like the ones that are closed that
this would be like under the closed issue
again.
Right, right.
All right.
And it's still being bootstrapped on that
particular process.
So I it's it's going through the,
you know, some of the the steps,
but not the whole state chart because it
hasn't been implemented yet.
OK.
Other questions on this?
Alrighty then, so let's go back.
To our go to our second slide.
Which is running implementation prompts.
But before we get into that,
I wanted to go into our project and show
you the prompts that I captured.
Let me bring up the.
The the the file was so we have a saved
prompts. So let me bring this up here.
So um.
Um.
So that what I did after after the the
session yesterday is I.
I said I first question thing I asked A I
was you know does this plan implement all
of the epics in the in the the
requirements document that we created and
it came back with an answer that it you
know it was only implementing the version
1.0 and there were other versions.
In the requirements document that weren't
included in the slices and that was
explaining because I was like what I was
curious about is why I ended up with only
two slices that had very rudimentary
implementations. When I saw more,
there was more work that was scheduled to
be done inside of the the.
The requirements document.
So I wanted to kind of get to that and
then so I went on to say also propose
additional features to the calculator
requirements and so it it went through
and added a whole number of additional
requirements for more more advanced
capabilities.
For the calculator,
you know things like you know,
scientific features,
features for doing unit conversions,
things for actually sinking,
seeking calculators for multiple
different.
Different machines so that you can
actually collaborate on a on a on a a
calculation,
which I thought was an interesting
suggestion.
So there's so so basically it put a whole
bunch of additional requirements into the
file,
which was what I was really trying to
drive towards because I wanted to have a.
A significant backlog that we can look at
today. And so then I said, you know,
repeated the prompt that we had run
earlier,
which is basically create an
implementation plan using vertical slices
that then allowed us to implement or
provided the ability to to implement all
of these new features that were added
into the.
The into the project plan and then I
asked if the plan implements all the
features and I found out that no,
it doesn't. It didn't.
It only implemented the 1.
0 features and so then I asked it to add
the features for the other versions that
it had defined.
And then I asked it to create an
instruction file for showcasing that
features,
because we discussed this yesterday,
something that might be a good idea.
That way we would kind of avoid any
confusion about what actually needed to
be produced and that was worthwhile.
And then I'm after adding these new
features into into the next I I asked it
to go ahead and create an implementation
plan of using vertical slices for the
updated calculator project and that would
include.
The new showcasing its instructions or
any questions on this so far?
All right.
So then I had a more sophisticated or a
little bit bigger prompt that's asking
basically using the planning instructions
that were just create planning vertical
slice planning as well as the
implementation plan.
Create prompt for a prompt file for each
slice that will implement each slice when
the prompt is submitted and that the
prompt file contains the steps to execute
and not the implementation itself,
which is something I wanted to.
I wanted to wait and let them run the let
the let the prompt actually.
Do the implementation,
not the not this prompt and then also
wanted to include verification steps that
should pass or must pass and then a
showcase for each slice.
When I when I got that back,
I said update the implementation plan
with a diagram because I wanted to see
what the dependencies are between slices
and what slices could be implemented in
parallel.
And I'll show you that diagram in a in a
minute.
And then I asked it to to include all the
vertical slices which it determined that
there were.
30 of them now and I asked it to remove a
a Sprint and duration estimates because
it the the implementation plan was broken
up into phases with different releases
and I I I instead wanted to wanted to.
Treat this as a a continuous stream of
work, you know,
without any time boxing around the work.
The idea would be we just start off with
the most the most the essentially start
off with with a a vertical slice which is
a foundational slice and then we get.
And then we could execute as fast as
possible. And so you know it had,
it had like a a four week implementation
plan that that had built just to get to
the version one of this and none of that
was I think useful for our exercise here.
And so it came up with a much simpler
implementation plan that is just focused
on implementing the vertical slices and
doing them in a in a way that that
respects the the, the,
the required dependencies between each
slice.
And that's really what I was going to
drive towards.
And then I had an issue with it getting
to render the diagram, which it fixed.
Here you can see that I it displayed it,
but there was an error,
so it fixed that error.
I often see this when I'm trying to
generate diagrams that they don't render
the first time and you have to go back
and.
And prompted AI to fix them.
Then I asked it to remove the phases from
the plan and that it should be a
continuous stream of work is which I
described it. So this is when it went,
it went through and simplified that plan.
I changed the diagram from.
From ortrait to landscape so that it
would.
It would it would render better.
And then um.
And then I asked it in the diagram to
shade the the the slices either in red or
green.
So that I could I could see which ones
can be implemented in parallel and which
ones could be which were which can't and
and therefore must be implemented by
themselves. Then I didn't like the colors,
so I asked it to change the colors a
little bit.
I I said and then create separate files
for each issue.
So with the idea of then creating an
issue for each slice,
create those separate files.
It looks like that's I recorded that one
in the log twice.
I said then remove the milestones from
the files that it created because I
didn't really don't really care about
putting milestones together about which
would tie us back to the versioning.
And then I said go ahead and create the
issues. So if we were to go to GitHub.
But let me go to before I do that,
let me bring up the.
implementation plan.
And that's this guy here.
So this is the implementation plan as as
modified by that the prompts that I just
ran.
So basically it's based on the product
requirements document document and it's
also using the vertical slice
implementation planning instructions to
actually.
Which describes what this document should
contain,
so it's using a combination of action
decomposition and feature based slicing.
It then has the road map.
This has phases in it,
but to so that's probably something I
wouldn't want to try to address,
but it basically talks about the the each
slice and we can see here that we got we
have you know our 30 different slices.
And what the specifications are for each
slice.
Oh, I think I have the wrong document.
That's why it's this guide here.
I've been seeing this error.
This is the error that I've been seeing,
so let me go back and ask it to fix this
error.
Copy doesn't work all the time.
All right,
so let's think about that and we'll use
the rest of the documents since I can't
show the the diagram yet.
You know that has a legend that tells us
what we're looking at with the.
So the idea is to.
Uh,
you could create a bunch of issues in
GitHub that uh.
Basically call out what needs to be done
in terms of the implementation and we and
we also have in the project.
The actual prompts that we want to run.
So if we look at our prompt files folder.
Older.
Oh,
actually they ended up in a prompts
folder here.
And so here is the prompts that we would
run for each of the each of the.
Each of the slices and.
So here's so here's the diagram.
So it's fixed,
thinks it's fixed that and we can go back.
Here is I guess it was just flashed.
Now that come on.
All right, so all right,
so each one of them contains the
implementation steps that need to be done
to create creating the HTML structure.
Styling style the interface,
implement the logic.
What the acceptance criteria are and what
the verification steps would be.
What automated test should be implemented
and then how to showcase this which is
you know,
opening up the the page showing different
aspects of it and.
It tells them what files it needs to
create and what the definition of done is,
and each one will have all of these
activities. Yeah, Chris.
Just a quick question,
hopefully you have a quick answer.
The tags on issues.
I was just looking at the issues in
GitHub.
One of the problems I've had in getting
the issues auto created is that it wants
to attach tags and those tags weren't
created in in GitHub yet.
Yep.
Is it?
Are we able to use the CLI to create
those tabs,
therefore ask AI to create them before it
tries to create the issues?
That's exactly what I what happened and
exactly what it did if I was to look at
the.
Creating the GitHub issues.
I think we might see where it actually
had to go and do that.
But it may not be in this one.
That would be awesome.
Yeah,
so I think it would be a good idea to add.
Add to something along the lines of like
a a GitHub instruction file.
That you know that applies to when you're
actually creating an issue.
You know that if if it needs A tag to go
ahead and create the tag first,
but I don't see that output.
It might be in here someplace that I
can't find right now,
but it it or maybe it's here,
but I guess it's hidden in some of the.
the output that was generated.
So it says they're all created,
so I don't see where I can expand this.
It's got user 5 references, but yeah,
it it definitely can. Oh right here,
right.
All 19 custom labels were created
successfully and it did this on its own.
I didn't actually the issue is that the
so when I ran,
when it ran or tried to create the issues
at first it created this PowerShell.
Script to do that.
It used files that are in here that to
actually that to contain the actual
issues that it wanted to create.
Then when it looked at what the failures
were related to,
it found that they were related to the.
The labels not existing and so it went
and then created all all 19 of those
labels and then it went.
It went ahead and then created all all of
the issues and successfully.
So yeah, you can do that as well.
Great. Thank you.
You're welcome.
So let me see if I can bring up that
document again and close down our chat
for now.
It's not there.
We wanted to go to this guy.
And uh, let's bring him up.
Again.
Let's see if we can see that diagram.
Let's maybe it's at the end.
Yeah, we're still getting the same error,
so let's.
Oops.
The notes.
OK.
I see why I have to do this twice.
And the the purpose of this diagram is
just a a dependency graph that gives us a
sense of you know what things are
dependent on each other so that we can
order,
so we can do the work in the proper order.
And as well,
it gives us the opportunity to execute
the the implementation in parallel and
that's the goal that I want to achieve
today.
So the idea would let me go back to the
slide because I think that has what I'm
asking us to do.
So we want to execute these
implementation prompts and we want to use
our custom chat nodes to do this if we
need to.
And then what I'm asking you to do is to
pair with somebody else, right?
Pick your pairs and then assign a a an
issue, a slice issue in GitHub.
To both of you and look to see if there
is a dependency on another slice which is
what documented in the issue itself so
that when it created the issues that also
included anything that would it would be
dependent upon and there's.
There's only one issue that isn't
dependent on something,
and that is the foundation slice that
needs to get created.
So if there's somebody that if you have a
dependency,
then work with the owners of that
particular slice to to.
To help them resolve that dependency so
that you can proceed with your own slice.
You want to review the slice
implementation prompt for errors and
admissions.
Make sure that you're in agreement that
the AI had generated that implementation
instructions correctly.
So that you think that it's going to be
successful,
then you can go ahead and run the
implementation prompt on a on a branch of
the the Greenfield branch.
So if you took a a branch of the of the
Greenfield branch yesterday,
you would want to update that branch with
with all the with the changes that have
been.
Pushed onto the that Greenfield branch or
you can just take a new branch off of the
Greenfield branch and that will
automatically have those those changes
that have been committed.
Once that implementation is finished,
you can review that implementation and
see if there's anything that you'd like
to change about that implementation.
You want to make sure that it that it and
verify that it the implementation passes
those verification checks.
I mean it should it.
The AI should verify them before it
completes the implementation,
but you can go back and say.
And ask the AI to verify that
implementation.
You could use a different model to verify
that implementation by asking it to look
at the verification steps and execute
them and you can you can go through and
do the verification yourself.
Once you're happy with that
implementation,
go ahead and create a PR and.
And let copilot also do its review and if
it finds anything that you should take a
look at,
go ahead and either ask AI to do the
implementation or do make the changes
yourself.
And then once you're happy with that.
And all your if in any test pass that
were implemented or all passing,
you can go ahead and then approve that.
That implementation approve that PR and
then merge that and merge that branch
back to the the Greenfield branch so that
we can now pull from that Greenfield
branch again and get started on on on the
next.
Batch of changes. If we can manage it,
it would be a good idea to switch pairs
so that you're working with different
people every time we we pick up a new
issue and then we just repeat this and
see how far we can get today in doing an
implementation.
And the other thing I would ask is let's
you know when you're communicating,
let's try to do our communication and the
main the main teams conversation.
But if you really feel that you want to
have a a side conversation with your pair,
you I can I can create a.
A a room where you can actually have that
conversation,
but I'd prefer everybody just to kind of
have that communication in the main main
chat. It might get a little disorganized,
but.
It'll give everybody a kind of an insight
in how everybody is proceeding and any
issues that come up,
we can kind of discuss them together.
All right. Any questions on this?
Exercise.
Sorry if I missed it. Are you gonna be?
Are you pushing up your prompts?
That you already have created there and
that's what we're working from.
No, no, the the the the the prompt files.
Yeah,
they're already committed into the the
repository on the Greenfield branch, so.
I tried pulling that down and I don't see
them.
They're in the props folder.
Oh.
You know what? I bet I probably am. No,
I'm not working off of a Ford.
This is the 20260209.
Yes, not the not the BF one,
not the brownfield one, but the 2026209.
It's the Greenfield.
Greenfield.
The only changes I have are the changes
that have been just made recently to the
change prompts and the and I added the
slides for today's course there so I can.
I'll push those up, but.
You should be looking at a a folder.
Called prompts.
And this content should be very similar
to what you see in the issue.
What was I looking for?
Copy the relative path.
Let me put that into chat.
Uh, OK, I do have them. Um.
I had to.
I must have had some leftover stuff from
yesterday.
I had to reset to Origin Greenfield and
then pull again and now I've got them all.
Thanks.
All right,
so you want to did you do that through
the UI or did you do a command for that?
I did it through CLI so get reset dash
dash hard origin slash greenfield and
then get bold.
Just go ahead and paste that in the chat.
That way if somebody else needs it,
they can.
They'll have it because I think Al's
having the same issue and Chris has made
a comment that the A I resources that
Uncle Bob made the list,
which is a good thing. Thank you,
Christopher.
So I would encourage you to go up in.
And you know pick your pair and and
assign the assign a a a a slice to your
your your pair.
That way you reserve that work for you to
do and then you can you can start
evaluating the.
The implementation prompt and the the
issue and see if you understand what it's
actually trying to accomplish.
All right, so.
Christopher is looking for a a a partner,
so if you have somebody who could join
with him, that would be a great idea.
So we should just kinda make a separate
uh meeting like just.
Well, I would, like I said,
I'd encourage you to have your
conversations here if we can manage it.
If it if it gets too hectic,
I'll I'll create a a a chat room that you
can use,
but I I think it would be valuable for
everybody to hear.
What what everybody's saying and if you
guys have got, you know Christopher,
you've got if you've got slice one and
slice one is is the.
The slice with the with the most
everything is dependent upon this
particular slice to get finished.
So why don't you go ahead and and start
that and we will monitor your progress
here.
Feel free to share your screen if you
want to.
And we can essentially kind of mob right
now on this one slice and everybody can
can can participate in the implementation
and and guiding that.
This will give us all a sense of what it
takes and then you can then.
Proceed with the other slices.
OK.
You'll see my screen here.
Yep.
Right. So and Dan,
since we're preparing together,
you speak up also whenever so the.
First step was review the slice
implementation prompt for errors and
omissions.
Sorry,
but the maybe I should have mentioned. Oh,
it does work now. OK,
I had my preview stopped working
yesterday.
So we'll review this for errors and
omissions.
Just talking about create the HTML
structure, add the container button grid.
HTML and RA label style the interface.
Large high contrast font.
Display zero clicking number buttons,
appends digits.
OK, so I mean this is this is pretty,
pretty straightforward.
So compare this with what was it what's
in the actual prompt file,
just to make sure that you're that the
prompt is essentially the same thing as
what is in the issue. It should be,
but you know I had AI create it,
so it's also possible that it.
It would deviate in some fashion,
so I would.
All right, so that is.
It's in the prompts folder.
Oh, the issues are in the front folder,
so.
Well, the others, yeah, that's the prompt.
So that's prompt one.
They said the issues are issues up here,
OK.
And the the issues are there.
So that should be the that should be what
was actually pushed into the repo and
then which is what that should be the
exact same thing because all it basically
did was to suck that in.
But that's what was initially created was
what the.
The issue was,
so this is the source of that and again
all that was derived from the
implementation plan and.
Are these issues up on GitHub or they
could be issues on GitHub?
There, there, there are both.
So here in in case you you wanted to to
see what the original source document was
that created the issue,
but they're also in GitHub, right?
And you make sure you've assigned
yourself the the issues.
Anybody not have a pair that they and has
not selected a a slice to take on?
So one thing that I'm seeing here,
it's the slice issue has something talks
about state management.
I don't know that I saw state management.
Sorry I lost track of where I was there.
State reads calculator state.
Oh, it does have states. Wait.
Yeah, I see it in both.
OK,
I'm I'm actually previewing the wrong one
here.
Let's move this out.
It keeps previewing, sorry.
Search for state in here create state
object create to track current inputs.
The issue calls for current value in
display org.
I got you displayed.
Nothing related to current value.
I'd be interested to see what it does.
On state change recurrent value.
So it it seems like it left out some
specifics.
Yeah, I'm seeing that too. There's no,
yeah,
it's not showing like the the display
when you when you press numbers and it's
it's not really clear that there's like a,
you know,
an area where it's updating and showing
the numbers as you're clicking them.
That that probably should be under #1,
the implementation step so.
One of these prompts get created again
like do.
So if you wanna recreate this prompt,
we find something missing then.
How do we do that?
We don't just update the prompt directly,
Well,
where where do we think that the the
do we or?
change need to be made?
Do we need to meet?
Does it need to be made in the issue?
Is it a problem with the issue or is it a
problem with the prompt?
Because the prompt is what we're going to
execute.
It's.
Well,
if if the the the VSO one is kind of the
source of truth and then I see an issue
with the prompt,
but I I figured we'd let copilot tell us
if there's.
I should have asked them to tell me if
there's anything different.
But it's looking for some differences.
Implementation prompt treats VS 01 as a
combined display and input slice,
while VS 01 defines it strictly as a
display only query slice.
The prompt appears to merge,
which should likely be two separate
slices,
one for display and one for number input
buttons.
I don't know that that's accurate 'cause
it does call for.
So how are all those prompts generated
again?
So we have the the slices which are the
issues.
Well, if you there is a there's a file,
there's a file called under requirements
France, but it will be.
called which is the implementation plan.
There's two of them. One of those,
one of those is obsolete.
It needs to be removed,
but the one that says enhanced is the one
that was used to actually generate it.
And if we go to the there's a the the the
saved prompts for.
File that you can see the prompt that I
used that combined this with the
requirements document in order to produce
the actual slices.
So if you're interested in seeing that,
then then take a look at that file and
the and the requirements file.
So when you're saying to say create the
slices,
that created the the slices prompt and
then and also created the implementation
prompt at the same time.
Don't know. Well,
the prompts are the implementation
prompts.
That's what we're looking to to get to,
right?
So like I said,
look at if you open up the save prompts
file, which is what I showed earlier,
it would.
Yeah.
It would have a.
It would have a prompt in there that
would basically is basically asking the
copilot to take a look at this
implementation plan enhanced and this
requirements document and produce a
slices.
For implementation.
OK,
so it looks like he first made the
implementation prompts and then from
there he made the issues. Is that right?
Yes, that that is correct.
But I said then OK ahead,
OK.
let's create issues from for the create
an issue for each of these prompts and
there might be an issue with that that
prompt that I use that might cause these
differences that we're seeing.
Between the issues and the prompt files
themselves, but I'm curious about.
So it did.
This caught that there was no mention of
calculator state in the prompt regarding
the current value display area,
but then it caught it.
You know it's saying it can be more
specific with contrast ratios.
No display error flag handling and so.
Does the issue see this is where it's
like is it making stuff up or is it
actually saying that?
Well it they it does have display area in
here render error message so is error
message so there's no.
Mention of error handling in the prompt.
But the this VSO one does specify render
error messages if this is true.
Um.
Truncation for long numbers.
Yeah,
so so there are there are some things in
the in VSO one that were not included in
the prompt which that seem important.
That's interesting because the prompt was
created 1st and then the issue was
created second.
Well, well,
I'm not talking about that unless I'm
misunderstanding.
I'm not talking about the issue,
I'm talking about the well,
I guess this is in the issues folder,
the VSO 1 dot MD.
Yeah.
So OK, so I have it backwards.
The prompt was created and then from the
prompt John you created the VS 01.
Yeah,
so as I that was you can see a prompt in
OK.
there where it's create, you know,
GitHub issues and it ended up creating
those issues in into individual files and
I think that that's what you're seeing
here under the issues folder.
But if you go into the prompts folder,
you should see all of the prompts.
OK.
So those that's what you're going to look
to try to implement.
Yeah, that I see.
OK and so So what I've done here is I
compared.
The issue that was created from the
prompt and it seems like the issue
Right.
contains more specific details than the
prompt. Um.
Which is which is odd, but you know,
are they significant differences?
And then we can ask AI to, you know,
update the prompt with whatever findings
that you have here.
Yeah, I mean,
I would say that some of them,
some of them I would say are significant
like state management,
error display and things like that,
but like the contrast ratio.
You know,
being more specific on the font size,
I'm just gonna say yes update.
I created a new branch for this.
Nope, that's not what I meant. Sad phone.
So if we wanted to update these like do
we want to go back to the implementation
plan?
You you could.
Or do we just update the prompts directly
or the issue directly?
Well,
it depends on the nature of the problem.
I think if we see this problem over and
over again and all of these slices are
different from their from their
implementation and at the I mean their
issue and the issue contains information
that's.
Not in the prompt.
Then we would want to go back to the the
prompt that we used to create it and the
source documents that it used and see if
we can ask AI to help us figure out,
you know how that how those differences
were.
Created.
You know we could ask and say well you
know this prompt produced this output.
When I created an issue from it,
it added additional content that I don't
see in the in the prompt and try to get
to the root of the the root of that and
see where you go from there.
This is interesting. It didn't add.
I think I messed it up with the font. Um.
Yeah,
because I asked it to review the issue
and the prompt.
I asked AI said it found a, you know,
critical issue that the scope mismatch.
So one option is just to split it into
two to two issues.
Or you know,
split it into two slices or kind of
rescope it.
Yeah, well,
that's something that you can do as well.
Or you can.
But I guess we would want the
implementation plan to be updated like if
we split into more than one scope,
we probably want to update the
implementation plan that that.
That we're doing that, I would think.
Correct, Brian.
And if you did that,
you could then go back and run the the
run the prompt that created the the
slices from the implementation plan and
have it, you know, regenerate.
You know,
just just the foundational slice or just
slice one and see what it see what it
proposes that we do because right now you
know I'm working on a branch so.
You can.
The only thing that we have to be careful
about is changing the issues,
because that's only one copy of that.
But in in my mind,
it's a good idea to keep them aligned,
but it's not imperative.
OK.
Yeah.
So on a on a on a brand new project you
we probably wouldn't create all of these
issues and prompts right away.
We probably want to like create the first
one for the smallest piece of
functionality to make sure it's doing
what we want before we go through and
start.
Creating them in mass is that.
That's a problem. That's probably correct.
I mean you you definitely.
Want to make sure that the implementation
plan is meet your expectations before you
actually start, you know, implementing.
Mhm.
I guess as we develop instruction files
that we're using from project to project,
we'll have more confidence in.
in the app, you know, right?
Yes, it's even including snouts,
including the truncate.
So Dan, if you're good with this,
I'm gonna go ahead and keep it and then
try and run it.
And then try and run it.
Sure, let's see what happens.
Alright.
Battles to create.
We could also use one of the agents,
right John? Like if we wanted to um.
Good point.
Sure you could do a session since this is
the.
Foundational slice.
Everybody else is depending on it that be
implemented. We should probably.
Do this in the foreground and justice
watch what it does.
Am I gonna have to push this to a fork in
order to create a pull request?
Mhm.
I mean, as long as you're on a branch,
you should be able to create a pull
request and then from that branch to push
back to the Greenfield branch.
You just want to make sure when you
create the PR that it's going to the
right source branch.
I'm assuming I wouldn't be able to push
there though.
I'll speak.
I mean,
you're still thinking about
implementation.
Yeah.
I have to get the.
To my um.
It is logged in as my work account which
is not on.
So I'm gonna while that's working,
I'm gonna switch.
Yeah.
Alright,
so it's seems to be working along.
Alright, some interesting messages about.
Well, it looks like it implemented it.
It took a first pass at the
implementation,
but then it did not meet the the
requirements precisely,
so it's going ahead and updating that.
So that's interesting.
So even even though we gave it the prompt,
it's still checking it against BSO one.
I guess that's mentioned in here.
Yeah, it should be.
Oh yeah, it was.
And so.
It's updating some some of the code,
so it's continuing to work on that the
basic index dot TS files and the index
dot HTML.
So I think it thinks the tests are
complete.
This.
Now it's going to try to run the tests.
But.
You can see that it's changed 8 files.
All right, so.
So what are you doing now, Christopher?
Now it's trying to install all the
packages.
I need to because I'm not going to be
able to push to this repo the way that
I'm logged in right now.
It's trying to figure out how to switch
to my personal.
GitHub unless you can.
You send me the files,
I could try to ush them on a new branch
for you.
See.
John, can you?
'Cause you added us all to that repo,
can you add this user to the repo you?
Actually,
I'm not sure that's gonna work because.
It's a GitHub Enterprise account.
Well, if we if this is gonna bog us down,
why don't we switch to let Dan drive?
Yep, sounds good.
And then uh.
He he can do all,
he can do the work on the PR.
Yeah.
So I will.
What I'll do here is.
Right now it's just installing so if this
patch file.
It's patch file might be big but.
Going to upload this patch file Dan so
that.
You can um.
So Alan.
Another option would be just to have Dan
start the prompt itself.
OK. Do you want to do that? Um.
Sure. So just um.
I'll stop sharing.
But just re-execute the the prompt, right?
We just execute the implementation prop,
correct?
The pump, that's correct.
All right.
Alrighty.
I don't think I put it into a folder.
I think I just put it right in the root.
We can deal with that afterwards.
You can now move it into a a separate
folder.
Hello.
Yeah.
So.
Tada, we have a calculator.
Mm-hmm.
All right,
so what's the next step according to our
instructions?
You want to review the implementation so
that that we're happy with the actual
code it wrote.
And we want to also take a look at the
verification steps in the in the prompt
to make sure that we're satisfied that it
actually.
Completed those verification steps and
then then it's about creating the PR.
Oh yeah, I made a verification file.
That must have been in the implementation
plan then, right?
That's how I knew how to do this.
Well, it should be a part of the prompt.
There should be a verification step.
I don't think we told it specifically to
create a file,
but that's that's a good idea.
So it's actually giving these manual
verification steps. Um.
I guess I can.
I don't guess I don't need to do all of
them,
but I can do a couple of them and see how
it does with the responsiveness.
No, it's wait.
OK. Can you explain what you're doing?
Oh,
I was trying to figure out why mine was
different from Dan's.
I still had a a leftover implementation
plan from yesterday and mine.
My implementation plan was to do it in
React.
I didn't tell it to do it in React,
it chose that. Um,
so that's why my folder structure is so
different and it built a React that.
All right. And Dan,
just so so you so everybody can get the
benefit of what you're thinking,
could you just explain what you're doing
as you're going along?
Uh, yeah. Well, I just saw it put the um.
The files and just like the root folder
here, so I asked it to move it. Um.
Move them into a, you know,
a subfolder because we adding more to it.
I I didn't tell it where.
I just thought I'd see, well, OK,
where where is he going to put it?
I think they put it in a web web.
Right.
That makes sense.
Yeah, it's in the web calculator folder.
I don't know if we wanna have these docs
inside the.
Side this.
Yeah, well, I mean,
there's some specific to the validations
are specific to the web app,
so I don't think that's necessarily bad.
If we were to add a back end API at some
point,
we would put that in a different folder.
OK.
With its own read meeting.
So I'm.
I'm OK with it.
OK, I mean,
should I go to the manual steps?
Like there's like a in here they have
where is that file, the verification file,
but I want to come in here and like put
an X on all these manually.
Or not? Would you do that?
So.
You know, I've been.
That might be something that we would go
back and improve the prompt to say,
you know, you know, we want to, we want,
we want things to be automated and not we
not to do a manual verification
verification steps that then listed are
absolutely necessary.
So you know, so I I would,
I would say what they ask they are if
there are is test automation for all the
manual verification steps and see if
there's more test automation that we need
to do here.
And.
And that might be something that we have
to, like I said, go back,
be something that we find in the in our
review.
Of the implementation plan and of the
slices that we need to improve and we
possibly regenerate the implementation
prompts that don't include the manual
steps because the implementation prompts
should be automated.
Uh.
And then we should be able to determine
at the very end that the based on the the
verification steps that are automated
that it's working correctly.
Yeah.
Well,
should I do this now or or maybe we
should just kind of move on and and get a
pull request and do all that like not get
too bogged down.
Yeah, that's fine.
I think I mean that.
Christopher,
are you happy with the implementation
you've?
It's pretty straightforward.
Yep, looks good.
All right.
Alright,
so then I guess I'll make AI think I'm
not selling the Greenfield branch.
I'll make a.
New branch.
So we just call it slice one or any any
specific naming convention.
That would be fine.
You need to keep your changes. I see.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. Oh,
it looks like that's done, so that's good.
By the way,
I made this get ignored because every
time I change branches it like all this
BS stuff comes out.
It's OK if I commit this or you want me
to not commit the.
Yeah, yeah,
of course you would do this normally,
so the the the reason why you shouldn't
do it now.
OK.
Looks good, yeah. Thanks. Go and push,
yeah.
I think so.
And it's asking about creating a pull
request, so that's our next step,
so that's good.
Alright, I'll just.
And.
I noticed a copilot code review right
here in this interface.
Yeah.
Does that run the same processes online?
Yeah, that would do the same process.
Yeah, I tried.
I don't see copilot has been added as a
code reviewer.
So there we can.
The this the sun.
Yeah, that guy's there.
I don't think that works. Um.
Trying to open up the repo.
2.
OK.
Oh, I guess it did go through.
Yep. So it's it's thinking about it.
That's good.
All right.
So just kinda wait. Let's um wait for uh.
Yeah, we're gonna have.
We'll wait for it to tell us that we
actually have a.
Any comments on this code review?
We'll see where we go from there.
All right,
any questions while we're waiting for the
code review?
It should take a couple of minutes for it
to think it's way through this.
It's not a huge PR,
so hopefully we won't take turn on line.
It's probably just waiting for back end
resource to free up to do the review.
So what? What? What can we do? Like,
I guess we would just wait for the AI to
do its first review, right? Or.
Yeah, well, yeah.
I mean we we're done our,
we did our own review.
You could assign yourself to do or assign
Chris to do a review of it and he should
be able to go in to look at the code and
and assign or and approve that.
So I think that would probably be the the.
A good next step is to go ahead and see
if we can get.
Get another review of the code.
And so we'll still be waiting for this
this code review.
Other questions while we're waiting on
anything about about this process that go
No.
Yeah.
ahead.
I was wondering if this PR gets
associated with that issue or like is
there a connection between the two
records?
Yeah, there should be, yes. I mean,
if we go back and look at the PR.
Yeah, there's an issue there.
Looks like this was created at the same
time. But yeah, if we go to the Oh no,
this is the PR. That's that's true.
You should you should be able to see the
issue that it's associated with it.
And if we go to the top,
we can see that we want to merge 1 commit
into Greenfield from slices,
which is what we were expecting.
I think right under mentioned at copilot,
I think there's a feature implement
foundational webcat.
I think that's the issue.
Right.
Well, this looks like the.
The code.
Doesn't look like,
doesn't look like it got associated with.
That's this one, right?
Yeah.
Is there a way like um to?
Oh, in development.
I know in those are dev OPS you put like.
Excuse me, what was that?
On the right hand side,
there's a development section under
milestone.
And it looks like you can manually
associate the issues there.
OK,
I know like with Azure DevOps you put
like a pound and then the work item
number that usually associates it,
but I guess it.
That's something like when we when we
create the pull request.
Do we prompt to associate with the issue?
Yeah, I'm not sure because we did that.
We basically hit the button that
presented the the pull request, right?
I think if we go into the issue itself,
we can we can create the branch from
inside of GitHub and it will associate it
with that issue.
Mm.
So how are we doing on the code review?
Is it still thinking?
Yep.
How about this code review with Chris?
Yeah.
I am looking through it. Everything looks.
That's where it looks like it.
It didn't have that error.
Right.
I don't know if you remember when I said
when I assigned it from here,
it had that error.
Uh, there wasn't some error that came.
Oh,
I I I ask you guys to to to assign the
the work item to yourself.
So I would you can go ahead and do that
now.
With the idea that that you're now,
you know,
taking responsibility for that
implementation,
you'd also get notifications from GitHub.
And things change so.
Looks like it's, uh,
something happened here.
You think something's something's amiss
or just not?
Well, it's still waiting requests, right?
Like 'cause when I when I assigned it
And you can.
from here from VS code,
it did did give some weird errors on
there.
I wonder if that's.
There's any that's any part of why it
didn't work properly?
My neither.
You might need to refresh the page 'cause
I've got a pull request overview showing
now.
Oh, there it goes.
Oh, OK, left review comments.
All right, let's take a look at those.
Do you do you prefer looking in here or
looking in the clicking clicking on this
one which?
I think it'll basically it'll take you to
should take you down to where the change
was the comment was made.
I think I think it goes by the where the
files is.
All right, So what did that like?
Markdown files missing AI AI Providence
meta date details.
So we would have to go back into Visual
Studio code and ask it why it didn't add
provenance metadata.
Actually, can we?
So I'm looking at this now in in Visual
Studio code. Can we?
Um.
Here, right?
Yeah.
Can can you refer to?
Can you refer to specific?
Do you have to copy paste or can you
refer to specific comments?
Um.
Well,
there's a that link is that link that
should be that to that. Well,
it's looking at there's like there is a
summary page.
So it's looking at that summary page and
Yeah.
it's seeing that that doesn't have the
Providence.
Um, let's.
All right.
And let's take a look at some of the
other com comments.
Mhm.
So what is this one?
Something about the Dom elements.
Didn't like how it's accessing things in
the Dom.
Mm.
All right. Does that make sense?
So like you have to copy paste like you
can't just say fix it it looks like right?
I think that's true.
If we look at it in the browser,
can we can we assign it to an agent?
Or no, I was curious.
Yeah, I don't think so. I mean,
sometimes you'll see that that the that
it has a proposed fix in the in the in
the review PR review comments and you can
then click on that to actually implement
it.
It would show up next to the resolve
comment.
Button.
Yeah.
But it's not doing that for this one,
so we would have to ask AI to address it.
OK, so yeah,
so I guess I would just do fix this,
So this is.
right? I I mean just fix fix these issues.
Right, right.
And you can just base them all that you
wanted to take a look at here and.
It will take us that way we can.
Take care of all of them at the same time.
Yeah.
Might not have the context of exactly
where it's.
See what happens.
Yeah.
Alright, so it looks.
There's a lot of this like AI generated
stuff.
Like the like the markdown files.
It doesn't like the the metadata looks
Alright.
like.
Yeah. Well, that one will, I think we can.
We can ignore.
For now, maybe something.
Hold on a second. It's actually just a.
I noticed.
Go ahead.
Sorry,
I noticed that you can add the pull
request in the context there that little
in the chat input.
Oh, crap, that's.
Just wondering if that would pull in all
the comments.
So this one right here. Yeah,
this is in the context.
Yeah, it is now, yeah.
So what you could do is you could resolve
the the ones you don't want AI to fix or
address and then ask you to address all
of the unresolved.
Comments.
Right.
Alright.
And when you see these read to allow read
only operations here,
if you use that drop down next to it,
you can approve them going forward either
just for this one.
Session or, you know, for all time.
Yeah.
So then we can push these changes and
have it. Uh.
I guess we should resolve the comments
and then push the changes and have it
review it again.
I think, yeah,
I think if you hear all the comments,
you can request another code review.
So you can see here allow that exact
command line or whatever, whatever it is.
I don't know if I have that exact command
line again. It was pretty specific.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, but.
And you're right. You're right about that.
All right,
so it looks like the things are all
resolved.
I'm going to run it in my in my browser.
Alright, that looks.
Looks pretty good.
This doesn't very.
So you're committing the changes.
Do you need to keep them first, right?
Good to do that.
You can go ahead and mark those and
resolved in the PR.
Just to be.
Another thing you could do is you can ask
AI to verify that it still that all the.
Verification things are have been
addressed.
So here in in this AI or actually I wanna
ask for another review here, so let's.
Um, let me go back to the the website.
This is the issue.
All right,
So what are you trying to do now?
We request review.
Alright, so it looks like there is a.
So then you said to verify the check the
verification, is that?
So if you look at the prompt file,
at the bottom of the prompt file,
there should be a list of verification
steps.
So there's like a definition of done at
the bottom.
And where's some places there should be
acceptance criteria, but that look um.
Except for the manual verification steps,
I think the acceptance criteria should be.
Thanks.
So if you you don't even need to paste it,
you just need to have that document in
your context and then just ask it to
verify the accepted that it the
acceptance criteria are so good.
Mhm.
And so this will do the A I will check on
this.
Usually this will be whenever it made a
modification like with this before I
would you know do a final approval and
make sure that those that the A I agrees
that it's completed those verification
steps and those would be things that we
would want to make.
Potentially continue to.
Verify.
Another thing that you could do that
might be useful would be when you
actually generate the slices.
You could ask it to, you know, verify any.
Any any slices that this particular or
slice depends on,
you know this is not applicable for this
one, but for the the next ones that we do,
we want to make sure that these
acceptance criteria are continue to
continue to to pass as we implement more
and more slices.
So it looks like it's done a verification
and it's not just summarizing that
conversation history.
Anybody have a question on this?
All right.
It's retty slow.
Yep.
Must be a lot of people doing code
reviews this on a Friday.
Another verification report,
so it looks like we're just about
finished.
All right, almost done, I hope.
So the other thing that we could do is
like a look at the showcase.
And just walk through those showcase
steps.
All right, so it liked.
And like what we did there, that's good.
OK, so showcase steps.
That's we have to do that ourselves,
right? Or or we can have.
But the idea here is that you would be
showcasing to the rest of the team the
work that you guys did on this one slice.
That would the idea being that as we add
new new features,
we can then show them to stakeholders
that aren't directly involved in the
implementation that.
That you you can you completed those
steps.
OK.
So.
So we look at the calculator and then we
can kind of go through that those steps,
Alright.
but it should be should be pretty quick,
right?
Yeah.
I made a big window here.
Well,
I don't know if this is exactly 1024 with,
but.
Yeah.
Something like that. Um.
So yeah.
Go design. So hey, hey everyone,
here's our modern calculator UI with a
clean display and numbers grid.
See how numbers append naturally.
As refreshed and the Cullen.
Look how intelligently leading zeros are
handled. It doesn't. It removes it.
And it works beautifully on all devices.
And here I'm chatting through so.
Also works.
With full keyboard navigation support,
so we have a solid,
accessible foundation that all features
will build upon.
Very good. Very good. All right, let's.
Push the let's merge that PR and let's
everybody can get started.
On the next.
No, that's not. That's a uh.
It's a it's.
It's a referred to a tactical. Yeah,
very good.
Where do I complete the PR? Sorry,
I haven't really used GitHub very much.
It should be down there. No, you don't.
You gotta you wanna merge that pull
Oh, what? Oh, merge.
request.
OK.
Don't delete the branch,
we'll just leave the branch out there.
I don't uh, the slice, the slice branch.
Yeah.
OK.
So people can see that and be able to
look at it later.
All right, so the it's closed and merged.
That means that we're now in a position
to work on the next group of slices.
So go ahead and assign yourself.
If you're participating in this exercise,
go ahead and assign yourself a a slice or
a pair up with somebody and do and do a
slice.
Dan and and Christopher really appreciate
this.
But do you guys have to pair with
somebody else and and and let's go ahead
and and start on the next we got a you
know 510 minute.
Before we can take a break,
and so let's just at least get a start on
it.
All right. Anybody have any questions?
All right, great.
All right, so the idea of is when you um.
Yeah, go ahead and.
Pair up with somebody and start working
on a on a on a one of your on a slice and
then when you've.
You think that you're ready to merge your
PR into the Greenfield branch.
The that's we'll do a showcase just like
Dan just did, and we'll go on from there.
All right. So I'll I'll leave you to that.
So in 5 minutes we'll take that break and
then I'll see you guys back at.
at one o'clock my time.
No, that's not true.
You'll be 11.
Are people just assigning issues to
themselves? Is that how this is?
Yeah,
the idea would be is this if you're going
to pair with somebody, you both assign,
assign both people to it.
If you want to work on your own,
go ahead and assign an issue to yourself
so that people know that you're working
on it.
And then go ahead and go down the steps
that I outlined in the slide and I can
share that slide again.
Again to proceed with, you know,
the review and the implementation of that
of that specific slice.
So we we can meet in about an hour, right?
Yeah, yeah.
All right, I'll see you in an hour.